the late 70s early 80s was a lot all right thousand songs in your pocket remember this ipod launched
october 23rd 2001 it changed everything i didn't know that i i'm calling this up because i i wrote
some information on this 2004 podcast coined in the guardian ipod plus broadcast podcast and 2022
apple discontinued the last ipod i thought that was nice before radio station decided what you heard
now you carried your own station your pocket when you're watching a guy broadcast live well now you're
watching me i'm here this is my home office i know i know i know what you're thinking it's amazing well
i try i do what i can all right so a few comments walkman disman zoom roast the zoo and gently all
right now we went from cassette tapes to the cloud right so gen x lived through every format change
thank you very much i think we survived you got the boomers that didn't want to deal with the
technology but that was kind of cute that adaptability is the asset now so make sure we used to rewind
tapes and being them and then streaming them remember that format change yeah ai yeah it's a little bit
bigger of a format change i like to talk about that so ai there is no way to tell anymore and that's only
going to get better there is no um way to be able to see the difference in these things so you're going
to be dealing with customer service very very soon and customer service is going to tell you that